{"data":[{"question":"If the United States had build more homes for poor people in 1955, the housing problems now in some parts of this country ___ so serious.","a":"wouldn't be","b":"will not have been","c":"wouldn't have been","d":"would have not been","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive) \n- We use type 2 because it's related to present","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"___ that the time will soon be ripe for intervention in Iran, they would be faced by a large army.","a":"It is believed","b":"Should they believe","c":"They would believe","d":"If they had believed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive) \n- Should can be stand at the beginning to stress","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I wish we ___ with my brother when he flies to England next week.","a":"could go","b":"had gone","c":"will go","d":"are going","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Wish + past simple: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled (type 2)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Sandra says that she wishes she ___ in New York now-","a":"have been","b":"be","c":"is","d":"were","answer":"4","explain":"\n-Wish + past simple: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled (type 2)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I wish I were as smart as you ___.","a":"have been","b":"had been","c":"are","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Wish + past simple: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled (type 2) (time speaking is simple present)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"William wishes now that he ___ English instead of French when he was in high school.","a":"have had studied","b":"studies","c":"had studied","d":"studied","answer":"3","explain":"- Wish + past perfect: : It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past (type 3)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I would rather she ___ tomorrow than today.","a":"come","b":"came","c":"should come","d":"has come","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Structure: Woud rather somebody did something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What will you do during the winter vacation? \" I don't know, but it's about time ___ on something.","a":"I'm deciding","b":"I'll decide","c":"I'd decided","d":"I decided","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Structure: It's time somebody did something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He would go to see you. \" ___ he did not come?\"","a":"What if","b":"Where if","c":"What come","d":"Why whether","answer":"1","explain":"\n- What if: used to ask what you should do or what the result will be if something happens, especially something unpleasant","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I would buy that book but I ___ enough money.","a":"do not have","b":"did not have","c":"will not have","d":"had not had","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}